<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Is Configuration Manager Dead</title><link>http://isconfigmgrdead.com/</link><description>Recent content on Is Configuration Manager Dead</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 09:37:09 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://isconfigmgrdead.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Steve Thomas and crew 2022-07-21</title><link>http://isconfigmgrdead.com/posts/ama-20270721/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 09:37:09 -0500</pubDate><guid>http://isconfigmgrdead.com/posts/ama-20270721/</guid><description>We release ConfigMgr three times a year and with each release there is at least a page of features. If you&amp;rsquo;re seeing feature dumps every four months it&amp;rsquo;s safe to say that the product is not on the path deprecation. &amp;ndash; Steve Thomas
The full conversation can be watched at AMA: Cloud-based device management with cloud attach - Tech Community Live | Endpoint Manager (and Youtube)
We used to put up at our conferences we put up big banners that say SCCM is not dead and then we started putting up big banners and say Configuration Manager is not dead and yet we still continually get &amp;hellip; from our customers all the time &amp;ldquo;when do I have to go to Intune because I know Configuration Manager is on a path to deprecation&amp;rdquo;, can you please, I don&amp;rsquo;t want to say for once and for all because we&amp;rsquo;re going to continually drive this home, can you like just verify the fact that Configuration Manager is not dead and we still continue to develop for it.</description></item><item><title>Danny Guillory 2022-06-22</title><link>http://isconfigmgrdead.com/posts/dannyguillory-20220622/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 10:15:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>http://isconfigmgrdead.com/posts/dannyguillory-20220622/</guid><description>Some customers even believe that ConfigMgr is dead&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;ll say it for probably the millionth time, Configuration Manager itself is not dead&amp;hellip; We [Microsoft] just want to help you [customers] do better and simplify with cloud&amp;hellip; we have tons of investment going into the on-premise state&amp;hellip; we are not taking down ConfigMgr.
&amp;ndash; Danny Guillory (Twitter | LinkedIn | Ignite), Senior Product Manager at Microsoft</description></item><item><title>ConfigMgr, Game Changer</title><link>http://isconfigmgrdead.com/posts/configmgr-gwblok/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 17:42:00 -0600</pubDate><guid>http://isconfigmgrdead.com/posts/configmgr-gwblok/</guid><description>I started with ConfigMgr in 2012 and it has changed my entire career path, and personal life. I had no idea that starting to use this tool also meant I was joining the most amazing community of professionals. The friends I&amp;rsquo;ve made and the skills I&amp;rsquo;ve learned because of this tool have been no small part of shaping the last decade of my life.
Thank you Microsoft Configuration Manager team and the community that makes this tool really great.</description></item><item><title>Steve Dispensa 2022-04-07</title><link>http://isconfigmgrdead.com/posts/stevedispensa-20220407/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 12:38:00 -0600</pubDate><guid>http://isconfigmgrdead.com/posts/stevedispensa-20220407/</guid><description>ConfigMgr is the largest deployed management solution in the known universe&amp;hellip; is core to our ability to deliver a complete solution&amp;hellip; we have no plans to end of life ConfigMgr. We love ConfigMgr. We just increased our development capacity on ConfigMgr. It&amp;rsquo;s nothing but a bright future for ConfigMgr. video</description></item><item><title>Aria Carley 2022-04-07</title><link>http://isconfigmgrdead.com/posts/ariacarley-20220407/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate><guid>http://isconfigmgrdead.com/posts/ariacarley-20220407/</guid><description>ConfigMgr is not only not dead, but coming soon it will be able to&amp;hellip; video</description></item><item><title>Brad Anderson 2019-10-04</title><link>http://isconfigmgrdead.com/posts/enternallifemem/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 22:33:12 -0400</pubDate><guid>http://isconfigmgrdead.com/posts/enternallifemem/</guid><description>i’ve been asked a couple times today if Microsoft Endpoint Manager means the death of #ConfigMgr —
honestly, the truth is really simple: MEM means ConfigMgr has eternal life!#MSIgnite pic.twitter.com/AeMp5eGxa7
&amp;mdash; Brad Anderson (@Anderson) November 4, 2019</description></item><item><title>Brad Anderson 2020-03-03</title><link>http://isconfigmgrdead.com/posts/futureofmem/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 22:33:12 -0400</pubDate><guid>http://isconfigmgrdead.com/posts/futureofmem/</guid><description>This video is something I’ve asked everyone in my org to watch. It was intended to be internal-only, but I can’t resist sharing it.
You can read more about why I think this is so important here: https://t.co/3jvzumi8EA pic.twitter.com/dd5IuoxcNt
&amp;mdash; Brad Anderson (@Anderson) March 3, 2020</description></item></channel></rss>